(Sheldon:)...thus assuring yourselves
a footnote in my memoirs...
(Sheldon:)...tentatively entitled
You're Welcome, Mankind.
(Sheldon:)All right, then. Just shout when you hear
the task you want to undertake.
(Sheldon:)Uh, dentist.
(Sheldon:)Okay, we can circle back
to that one. Um...
(Sheldon:)Who wants to take me Wednesday morning
to get new heels put on my dress shoes?
(Sheldon:)Anyone? Oh.
That one had "hoot" written all over it.
(Sheldon:)Um, all right. Uh, dermatologist.
(Sheldon:)Allergist.
(Sheldon:)Podiatrist.
(Sheldon:)Supercuts?
(Sheldon:)Okay, okay, here's a fun one.
(Sheldon:)Um, I need a new picture frame and
I have a hankering for Swedish meatballs.
(Sheldon:)Who wants to spend the day
with me at lkea?
- Their meatballs are good.
- What?
(Raj:)Nothing. Nothing.